<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SOTTOVUOTO</title>
    <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SOTTOVUOTO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 19:59:33 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Time To Hunt</title>
      <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/time-to-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 19:59:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/time-to-hunt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;사냥의-시간&#34;&gt;사냥의 시간&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;![Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m41s547](/home/yuja/Immagini/Movie snaps/Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m41s547.png)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Year:&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2020&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Director:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yoon Sung-Hyun&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Country:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;South Korea&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;time-to-hunt-was-probably-the-most-frustrating-movie-experience-i-had-recently-maybe-my-expectations-were-already-set-too-high-after-that-beautiful-movie-of-night-in-paradise-but-whereas-in-that-case-i-was-left-in-awe-in-this-case-i-felt-angry-and-dissatisfied-warning-may-contain-spoilers&#34;&gt;Time to Hunt was probably the most frustrating movie experience I had recently. Maybe my expectations were already set too high after that beautiful movie of &amp;ldquo;night in paradise&amp;rdquo;, but whereas in that case I was left in awe, in this case I felt angry and dissatisfied. Warning: may contain spoilers.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;In the near future, a financial crisis will hit Korea and slums arise.  From those areas, a group of young people commit crime to survive.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; So the summary says on Wikipedia.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I chose this movie looking for something light to watch and packed with action, so probably I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have expected a masterpiece in the first place. But nevertheless I did not enjoy it that much. First of all there something that felt &amp;ldquo;off&amp;rdquo; all throughout. Maybe it was the setting. That &amp;ldquo;dystopian future&amp;rdquo; that felt poorly developed in the plot and only functioned as a backdrop, but never felt really necessary for the story. Or maybe the characters, also a bit too stereotypical to be relatable and generally poorly developed as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was nothing about this dystopia that really had an impact in the story, and neither the atmosphere, if not just as a justification of the big &amp;ldquo;heist&amp;rdquo; that the street gang wants to organize, but nothing else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The kids are supposed to be &amp;ldquo;poor&amp;rdquo;, but you never get this feeling when they drive cool-ass looking cars, they sport sleek haircuts (talking to you, Ki-hoon) or they have expensive-looking phones. So they kinda look like a bunch or rich kids in a poor neighbourhood, even if that wasn&amp;rsquo;t completely intentional. None of them is really standing out with their personality, except maybe for Jang-ho, the most interesting one. But everyone else is so blank and stereotypical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dialogues are flat and they tend to be overly descriptive, completely missing the point of the &amp;ldquo;show, don&amp;rsquo;t tell&amp;rdquo; rule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But honestly the real flaw was the script itself. The cringe-y plot-twist where (spoiler alert!) the hitman step back from its misison makes you wanna give up with the rest of the movie. I mean, i get it. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the weirdness of the character, but come on! Doesn&amp;rsquo;t make any sense and at that point I was lost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What saves this movie from a failure is the good direction. Despite all the flaws previously mentioned, there&amp;rsquo;s a good build-up of tension that keeps you hooked till the final resolution, and the cinematography is  top-notch. Especially that moment on the road that seemed to be coming out of Valhalla Rising, and I don&amp;rsquo;t think it was completely a coincidence. On the contrary, it was a very cool reference that I appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honestly it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a completely &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;bad&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; movie. I think it had some good ideas behind, but they were poorly executed and the final product is not completely convincing. But hey! I&amp;rsquo;ve heard that Netflix &lt;a href=&#34;https://deadline.com/2021/11/squid-games-netflix-remake-korean-movie-time-to-hunt-adam-randall-1234871237/&#34;&gt;is going to produce a series&lt;/a&gt; out of this movie, so I guess I&amp;rsquo;m the only one who didn&amp;rsquo;t like it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So don&amp;rsquo;t take just my words. You may too end up liking it in the end!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visuals: ★ ★ ★&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Screenplay: ★&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall: ★ ★&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;![Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m52s390](/home/yuja/Immagini/Movie snaps/Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m52s390.png)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;![Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m00s114](/home/yuja/Immagini/Movie snaps/Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m00s114.png)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;![Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h53m26s228](/home/yuja/Immagini/Movie snaps/Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h53m26s228.png)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Night in Paradise</title>
      <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/night-in-paradise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 17:07:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/night-in-paradise/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;낙원의-밤&#34;&gt;낙원의 밤&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Year:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2020&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Director:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Park Hoon - Jung&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Country:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;South Korea&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sottovuoto/me/main/posts/images/Moviesnap2022-12-03-19h20m51s805.png&#34; alt=&#34;vlcsnap-2022-12-03-17h36m12s228&#34; style=&#34;zoom:120%;&#34; /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I finally watched &lt;strong&gt;Night in Paradise&lt;/strong&gt;, underrated beauty premiered for the first time at the &lt;strong&gt;2020 Venice Film Festival&lt;/strong&gt; but still quite unknown among the general public. The story follows the archetype of the classic Yakuza movie but with a softer, melancholic feeling attached. In some ways, it&amp;rsquo;s an allegory of life and death. Two elements that are constant in the whole movie. Despite the classicality, the movie manages to stay fresh and deliver an outstanding visual experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Main protagonist is probably &lt;strong&gt;Jeju&lt;/strong&gt;, the small island off the coast of South Korea. I never realized how beautiful that island was. The sensual cinematography really manages to capture its exotic and mysterious feeling. It&amp;rsquo;s a perfect location for this raw and solitary movie, and somehow it remind me of the desolation and despair that can be often perceived from Scandinavian noir, where human emotions are completely  overwhelmed by the surrounding nature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The island really convey that sensation of alienation and isolation from the outside world. You&amp;rsquo;re left alone fighting your own demons and there&amp;rsquo;s no helping hand to save you from this fight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even the relationship with the people around becomes difficult in these circumstances, as in the case with the complicated feelings between Tae-gu, the main protagonist and Jae-yeon, the girl that is hosting him on the island.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The movie is a beautiful tale of &lt;strong&gt;life and death&lt;/strong&gt;. And, as in the classic mobster tradition, it also explores the journey through a path of loyalty, betrayal and redemption of the main protagonist (and lots, lots of blood). But most of all, it was a really beautiful cinematographic experience with long shots of the silent landscapes and close-ups of people&amp;rsquo;s emotions. &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dark and poetic.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Recommended.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visuals: ★ ★ ★ ★&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Screenplay: ★ ★ ★&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall: ★ ★ ★ ★&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sottovuoto/me/main/images/vlcsnap-2022-12-03-17h34m21s685.png&#34; alt=&#34;vlcsnap-2022-12-03-17h34m21s685.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sottovuoto/me/main/images/vlcsnap-2022-12-03-17h35m54s203.png&#34; alt=&#34;vlcsnap-2022-12-03-17h35m54s203.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sottovuoto/me/main/images/vlcsnap-2022-12-03-17h35m39s624.png&#34; alt=&#34;vlcsnap-2022-12-03-17h35m39s624.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sottovuoto/me/main/images/vlcsnap-2022-12-03-17h36m44s052.png&#34; alt=&#34;vlcsnap-2022-12-03-17h36m44s052.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sottovuoto/me/main/images/vlcsnap-2022-12-03-17h39m10s987.png&#34; alt=&#34;vlcsnap-2022-12-03-17h39m10s987.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Experiment</title>
      <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/the-experiment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 18:40:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/the-experiment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So I started this thing recently. It&amp;rsquo;s my little self-experiment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I joined a small Korean Mastodon server. It was more of a curiosity, nothing really serious about it. But it&amp;rsquo;s been a week already in this new place and &lt;strong&gt;I really like it so far!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only two languages allowed: &lt;strong&gt;English and Korean&lt;/strong&gt;, so I&amp;rsquo;m forced to try both. To be honest, everyone just uses Korean so I end up using mostly that language. It&amp;rsquo;s still a bit awkward to me. I think it must be obvious that I&amp;rsquo;m not familiar with the language and I&amp;rsquo;m going a bit too far from what is comfortable to me. But, at the same, is quite an exciting challenge!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for me: I had a period in my life where I was serious about learning this language. I had this coveted dream to go and live in some East Asian country and I picked South Korea as an interesting destination for me, so that&amp;rsquo;s when I felt the urge to learn the language. Life then took another turn, years have passed, and I mostly lost the little I&amp;rsquo;ve learnt during that time. But I won&amp;rsquo;t forget the fond memories and the excitement that discovering a new culture can bring. And since then, I always wanted to go back to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I just needed the &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; excuse.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So the excuse finally came by joining this server.&lt;/strong&gt; I get by mostly through the translator (God bless it!), but I was amazed on how I could pick up some sentences, the things I still remember and those I still need to learn. The server is a perfect place to learn, and after a week I gotta say, &lt;strong&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m learning a lot!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What started as a joke is turning out as a very exciting experiment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are a few things that make this place work so well:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People just toot random things, and I can look and learn what people tend to say every day, rather than studying from grammar examples&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By translating and repeating words and sentences, I&amp;rsquo;m starting to see some grammatical patterns. Nothing big, but there are some things that start to get familiar (you know when something starts to sound &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; in your mind)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I can answer to someone and there&amp;rsquo;s a lot less pressure than 1:1 conversations. People answer to me if they want, and then they can go back to their business. There are plenty of other interesting people around, so I don&amp;rsquo;t need to &amp;ldquo;perform&amp;rdquo; in front of someone and keep a conversation going.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You just stumble upon conversations, and you don&amp;rsquo;t need to &amp;ldquo;create&amp;rdquo; new ones&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People are chill and quite welcoming!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m &amp;ldquo;forced&amp;rdquo; to use Korean most of the time. So there&amp;rsquo;s no shortcut to that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, there&amp;rsquo;s &lt;strong&gt;A LOT&lt;/strong&gt; that I still don&amp;rsquo;t understand and this thing bugs me. And this feeling of needing to know more is the best fuel to start learning again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And that&amp;rsquo;s what I did!&lt;/strong&gt; I took out the old and dusty memory cards and I got back studying them. Other than getting back to learning grammar and probably, in the future, watching some shows to get back to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s still kinda awkward. I still have to rely heavily on the translator (there&amp;rsquo;s no way I can hold the same conversation in real life!) and my answers to simple questions are a guessing game most of the time. &lt;strong&gt;But I really like how this experiment is going!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Steps</title>
      <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/7-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 15:49:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/7-steps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Congratulations! You came so far. You overpassed all the difficult trials, you fought against evil forces and you followed your master down the dungeon into this secret place of &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;spiritual healing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nah, I&amp;rsquo;m just kidding! It&amp;rsquo;s just my personal blog. It just started as an experiment and now I don&amp;rsquo;t know exactly what to write about except for random stuff like these. But you did take a long journey to come here, so that&amp;rsquo;s why I feel it&amp;rsquo;s my duty to reward your resilience by offering you my &lt;strong&gt;7 steps&lt;/strong&gt; of self-trascendence:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hvob - Oxid&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4QWIDvP9hM4&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.youtube.com/vi/4QWIDvP9hM4/0.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMAGE_ALT&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonobo - Defender&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-XBukgugjPU&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.youtube.com/vi/-XBukgugjPU/0.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMAGE_ALT&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kirinji - Killer tune kills me&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Y36b8_WFejI&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.youtube.com/vi/Y36b8_WFejI/0.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMAGE_ALT&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mariana Froes - Rosa e Laranja&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n1w76D8_ug8&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.youtube.com/vi/n1w76D8_ug8/0.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMAGE_ALT&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Anna Hisbbur - Before Bed&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I43CCaq52V4&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.youtube.com/vi/I43CCaq52V4/0.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMAGE_ALT&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mariya Takeuchi - Plastic Love&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=T_lC2O1oIew&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.youtube.com/vi/T_lC2O1oIew/0.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMAGE_ALT&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zin - Walk-in Closet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tug4snGLR24&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.youtube.com/vi/tug4snGLR24/0.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;IMAGE_ALT&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After you&amp;rsquo;ll complete the 7 steps, you will reach spiritual illumination. If not, come back again and we&amp;rsquo;ll reimburse you. This is not a scam, money back guaranteee. Call now!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 17:52:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;so-this-website-is-also-my-first-experiment-with-hugo--github-pages-and-one-of-my-very-few-experiments-with-developing-overall&#34;&gt;So this website is also my first experiment with Hugo + Github pages. And one of my very few experiments with developing overall.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know. Lame. But what else would you expect from someon that has never touched the code, if not for a couple of lessons at school? This website is only a place where I can park some thoughts and I wanted something simple and minimalistic, easy to deploy. I&amp;rsquo;ve read some suggestions online and I landed into this solution that involves Hugo as a static website generator and Github Pages as a hosting place. Ah, forgot to mention, I also wanted something to be free, so I don&amp;rsquo;t incur in the problem to have billings out of control. This solution satisfied me, in the end.
The only flip-side is that, with this method, you have to generate a new website each time you deploy a new edit or post. This is not the most efficient way to update the website, but maybe I&amp;rsquo;m just unfamiliar with it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First day</title>
      <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/first-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:57:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/first-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So here we are. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while, uh?
This is my first attempt to create an independent little website where I will talk about everything and whatever, so stick around.
Mostly I will talk about art, design, food, popular culture and the occasional rant.
I come from Mastodon, so you had probably met me already there. If not, I&amp;rsquo;m CONTESTO, go follow me! @contesto@mastodon.uno&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beside that, a little about me:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My name is Lorenzo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am 29 y.o.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I was born in Trento [IT]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I studied graphic design &amp;amp; communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I just started a little community about Japan on Feddit here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://feddit.it/c/giappone&#34;&gt;https://feddit.it/c/giappone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you like Weval, we can be good friends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
