<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ALTO CONTRASTO</title>
    <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/contrasto/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SOTTOVUOTO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 19:59:33 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sottovuoto.github.io/contrasto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Time To Hunt</title>
      <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/contrasto/time-to-hunt/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2022 19:59:33 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sottovuoto.github.io/contrasto/time-to-hunt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;사냥의-시간&#34;&gt;사냥의 시간&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;![Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m41s547](/home/yuja/Immagini/Movie snaps/Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m41s547.png)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Year:&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2020&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Director:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yoon Sung-Hyun&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;Country:&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td style=&#34;text-align:left&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;South Korea&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;time-to-hunt-was-probably-the-most-frustrating-movie-experience-i-had-recently-maybe-my-expectations-were-already-set-too-high-after-that-beautiful-movie-of-night-in-paradise-but-whereas-in-that-case-i-was-left-in-awe-in-this-case-i-felt-angry-and-dissatisfied-warning-may-contain-spoilers&#34;&gt;Time to Hunt was probably the most frustrating movie experience I had recently. Maybe my expectations were already set too high after that beautiful movie of &amp;ldquo;night in paradise&amp;rdquo;, but whereas in that case I was left in awe, in this case I felt angry and dissatisfied. Warning: may contain spoilers.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;In the near future, a financial crisis will hit Korea and slums arise.  From those areas, a group of young people commit crime to survive.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; So the summary says on Wikipedia.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I chose this movie looking for something light to watch and packed with action, so probably I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have expected a masterpiece in the first place. But nevertheless I did not enjoy it that much. First of all there something that felt &amp;ldquo;off&amp;rdquo; all throughout. Maybe it was the setting. That &amp;ldquo;dystopian future&amp;rdquo; that felt poorly developed in the plot and only functioned as a backdrop, but never felt really necessary for the story. Or maybe the characters, also a bit too stereotypical to be relatable and generally poorly developed as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was nothing about this dystopia that really had an impact in the story, and neither the atmosphere, if not just as a justification of the big &amp;ldquo;heist&amp;rdquo; that the street gang wants to organize, but nothing else.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The kids are supposed to be &amp;ldquo;poor&amp;rdquo;, but you never get this feeling when they drive cool-ass looking cars, they sport sleek haircuts (talking to you, Ki-hoon) or they have expensive-looking phones. So they kinda look like a bunch or rich kids in a poor neighbourhood, even if that wasn&amp;rsquo;t completely intentional. None of them is really standing out with their personality, except maybe for Jang-ho, the most interesting one. But everyone else is so blank and stereotypical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dialogues are flat and they tend to be overly descriptive, completely missing the point of the &amp;ldquo;show, don&amp;rsquo;t tell&amp;rdquo; rule.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But honestly the real flaw was the script itself. The cringe-y plot-twist where (spoiler alert!) the hitman step back from its misison makes you wanna give up with the rest of the movie. I mean, i get it. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the weirdness of the character, but come on! Doesn&amp;rsquo;t make any sense and at that point I was lost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What saves this movie from a failure is the good direction. Despite all the flaws previously mentioned, there&amp;rsquo;s a good build-up of tension that keeps you hooked till the final resolution, and the cinematography is  top-notch. Especially that moment on the road that seemed to be coming out of Valhalla Rising, and I don&amp;rsquo;t think it was completely a coincidence. On the contrary, it was a very cool reference that I appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Honestly it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a completely &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;bad&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; movie. I think it had some good ideas behind, but they were poorly executed and the final product is not completely convincing. But hey! I&amp;rsquo;ve heard that Netflix &lt;a href=&#34;https://deadline.com/2021/11/squid-games-netflix-remake-korean-movie-time-to-hunt-adam-randall-1234871237/&#34;&gt;is going to produce a series&lt;/a&gt; out of this movie, so I guess I&amp;rsquo;m the only one who didn&amp;rsquo;t like it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So don&amp;rsquo;t take just my words. You may too end up liking it in the end!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Visuals: ★ ★ ★&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Screenplay: ★&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall: ★ ★&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;![Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m52s390](/home/yuja/Immagini/Movie snaps/Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m52s390.png)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;![Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m00s114](/home/yuja/Immagini/Movie snaps/Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h48m00s114.png)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;![Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h53m26s228](/home/yuja/Immagini/Movie snaps/Moviesnap2022-12-08-16h53m26s228.png)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
